<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tours>

			<sites>
				<sitesId>9</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Discovery tours in St. Louis SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>3</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Discovery and Culture</packageTitle>
				<description>The city of St. Louis, located in the South West of Senegal, is a symbol of French colonialism. This explains the one hand that tourism in St. Louis is supported by its glorious past.  It is mainly a tourist you will find in the city of Saint-Louis, Senegal with its rich historical and architectural heritage. The city of St. Louis and one of the main tourist destinations in Senegal.  When traveling tourist in Saint-Louis, remember was the capital of Senegal, you will discover the famous Faidherbe Bridge, Governor's Palace, the Museum of the City ... Through excursions you will also discover the Park Langue de Barbarie and Djoudj Park, the third largest bird sanctuary in the world. To find accommodation during your stay tourist, look for hotels in Saint-Louis or rentals in St. Louis ads.</description>
				<prix>1000</prix>
				<accessiblite>5</accessiblite>
				<importance>5</importance>
				<image>map_avilabeach.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.saintlouisdusenegal.com/</liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>1</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Discovery tours Cape Skirring SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>1</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Culture and Discovery</packageTitle>
				<description>The seaside resort of Cape Skirring is located south-west of Senegal in the Casamance region. Beach tourism is the main attraction in Cape Skirring which houses one of the most beautiful beaches of Senegal with coconut and palm trees.  As Sally Portudal, Cape Skirring is very popular with tourists on holiday in Senegal. Find a hotel in Cape Skirring in consultation with advertisements on our tour guide.  The seaside resort of Cape Skirring is located a few miles from Kabrousse and about 70km from Ziguichor. We can help you explore this beautiful tourist site offering addresses of hotels, inns, campsites, restaurants.</description>
				<prix>750</prix>
				<accessiblite>0</accessiblite>
				<importance>3</importance>
				<image>map_bigsur.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.cap-skirring.com/</liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>5</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Sight Seeing in Goree Dakar SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>1</packageId>
				<packageTitle>History</packageTitle>
				<description>A pleasant stay in Dakar tourism inevitably discover the Island of Goree. The Goree Island, a World Heritage Site by UNESCO fascinated first by its colonial architecture. Goree therefore patie symbols of Senegal tourism and tourism in Africa because of its rich history linked to the slave trade. Enjoy your stay at Goree to visit including the house slaves, the women's museum, the Museum of the sea or the Fort d'Estrees which houses the historical museum where you can discover the history of Senegal. The boat crossing takes about 20 minutes. The tour of the island is on foot, walks through the streets lined with colonial houses on the island of Goree are nice.</description>
				<prix>1500</prix>
				<accessiblite>5</accessiblite>
				<importance>5</importance>
				<image>map_channel.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.mairiedegoree.org/page.php
    </liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>6</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Discovery tours in Palmarin Mbour SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>2</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Adventure</packageTitle>
				<description>Palmarin can be considered the most beautiful tourist sites in the Sine-Saloum, south of Little Senegal Coast. Palmarin itself is formed by the villages Palmarin Ngallou or Sessene, Palmarin Diakhanor, Palmarin Ngueth and Palmarin Gounoumane where coconut palms and bring originality to the landscape. Agriculture and fishing are the main activities carried out in the village of Palmarin. However, the beauty of the site to encourage the building of accommodation for tourism structures suddenly some palmarinois devoted increasingly to tourism. However the village of Palmarin is severely threatened encroachment of the sea having led to a deterioration of the ecosystem.</description>
				<prix>1500</prix>
				<accessiblite>5</accessiblite>
				<importance>5</importance>
				<image>map_ojai.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.palmarin.org/</liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>8</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Discovery tours of the islands of Saloum SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>2</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Adventure</packageTitle>
				<description>Our tour guide will accompany you to discover the Sine-Saloum tourist area located west of Senegal, about 150 km from Dakar. Tourism in the Sine-Saloum is favored by rich ecosystem, beaches and many species of birds. Sine-Saloum. is one of the most beautiful tourist sites in Senegal. This park is home to the tourist region of the Saloum Delta, Senegal second nature reserve, consisting of mangroves, forests and lagoons. The village of Palmarin is another attraction of the Sine-Saloum.</description>
				<prix>2000</prix>
				<accessiblite>4</accessiblite>
				<importance>5</importance>
				<image>map_pasadena.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.sinesaloum-tourisme.com/</liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>2</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Discover the village of Saly Mbour  SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>1</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Entertainment</packageTitle>
				<description>Tourism Mbour, Senegal has developed the reputation of the resorts as Sally Portudal, Somone and Niaming. The Department of Mbour occupies a prominent place in tourism in Senegal.  The department also houses Mbour other attractions that are well worth a visit: Warang, Ngaparou, Toubab-Dialaw Mbodiene or popenguine. Find out our guide addresses of travel agents or tour operators in Senegal specialized in organizing trips to Mbour to find out more about tours.  Mbour hotels offer luxury, exceptional service and comfort at the height of fame of seaside tourism in Senegal. We invite you to consult the various advertisements in this guide tourism in Senegal to spend a weekend or stay in Mbour.</description>
				<prix>1500</prix>
				<accessiblite>0</accessiblite>
				<importance>3</importance>
				<image>map_yosemite.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.salysenegal.net/</liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>10</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Discover the tourist region of Thies SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>3</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Society</packageTitle>
				<description>This is especially the seaside tourism that can be discovered in the region of Thies and Mbour department holds all the weight of the tourist area. In fact it does not really exist in the same tour in the town of Thies. However, recreation and accommodation facilities are not lacking in the city of Thies. Moreover, we offer this tour guide Senegal ads for you to find a hotel in Thies.</description>
				<prix>1500</prix>
				<accessiblite>4</accessiblite>
				<importance>5</importance>
				<image>map_ojai.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.thiers-tourisme.fr/</liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>7</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Discovery of tourist circuits in Dakar SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>2</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Society</packageTitle>
				<description>Business tourism has boomed in the city of Dakar, capital of Senegal, the concentration of economic activities in the country. Find your hotel in Dakar on our tour guide Senegal. With its mild climate, a holiday in Dakar is always nice. More Dakar Senegal is a city where there is the most fun. You can practice several activities: fishing horseback riding, tennis, golf, diving.</description>
				<prix>2000</prix>
				<accessiblite>5</accessiblite>
				<importance>5</importance>
				<image>map_various.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.dakarvoyages.com/</liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>3</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Sight Seeing Carabane Casamance SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>1</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Discovery and Culture</packageTitle>
				<description>The most prestigious historic site and former trading post of the Casamance River Carabane is a tropical island whose inhabitants have always offered you a friendly and warm welcome. The calm of the island hammocks await you for a nap, huge sandy beaches lined with coconut palms, lush paddy fields, visits to neighboring islands, and fishing parties will satisfy you fully.</description>
				<prix>1500</prix>
				<accessiblite>0</accessiblite>
				<importance>2</importance>
				<image>map_valley.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.casamance.net/</liens>
			</sites>
			
			<sites>
				<sitesId>4</sitesId>
				<sitesTitle>Tourist discovery Park Niokolokoba  Tamba SENEGAL</sitesTitle>
				<packageId>1</packageId>
				<packageTitle>Adventure</packageTitle>
				<description>National Park Niokolo Koba is one of the largest game reserve in West Africa. Created in 1954 to protect and conserve wildlife and endangered flora, the park is ranked since 1981 by UNESCO as World Heritage Site and Biosphere Reserve. With Badiar Park in Guinea since 1990 he formed the Transboundary Niokolo Badiar. Niokolo Koba is open all year round, but the best time to visit is from March to May is hot and dusty, but at the end of the dry season it is easier to see animals that are found near some water points that remain. The starting point for excursions is Tambacounda, 470 km south-east of Dakar, served twice a week by the Dakar train> Bamako.</description>
				<prix>2000</prix>
				<accessiblite>4</accessiblite>
				<importance>4</importance>
				<image>map_whitney.gif</image>
				<liens>http://www.niokolo.com/</liens>
			</sites>
			
</tours>